Fang-Yi, Chu

Web/UI Designer London,UK

+447477863158 imfangchu@gmail.com

https://fangchu.github.io/works/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/imfangchu/

I am a UI/WEB designer with six years industry experience. My focus is on high quality creative website and visual design with coding. I am skilled to solve any design problems with user-centred design techniques.

Work Experience

Freelancer

Web Designer / Developer, London August 2018 - Present

- Design (concepts, ideas, brainstorms, project planning, visual layout, responsive design) for website projects, Access Keys, XHTML / CSS / JAVASCRIPT.
- Plan brand of the local government art and literature industry, responsible for visual design, posters and card production.

Rakuya .Inc (Rental Websites)

UI Designer / Developer, Taiwan October 2014 - July 2018

- · Set standards for wireframes and user flows, created prototypes for user testing.
- Presented competitor analysis, usability research and design solutions to executive team.
- Redesigned and implement the sell/rent objects websites with the team, replacing the old website structure with a new one improving user experience on devices and increasing user visits from 30% to 70%.
- Responsible for UI design of web and mobile apps for website and networking systems.
- · Extensive experience building responsive websites utilising HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.
- Communicated and collaborated with the development team and marketing team to ensure that designs are delivered as per the brief set.
- Optimised SEO of the website which led to increased marketplace lead generation and increased conversion rates.

Grazingcat Design Studio

Web Designer, Taiwan October 2013 - July 2014

- Designed the UI, and interaction flow of new web and mobile applications.
- Designed startups' web and mobile apps including strategies, interaction design and visual design. This received high ratings on customer satisfaction surveys.
- Responsible for planning and developing e-newsletters and operating facebook media while bringing the most popular articles to the newsletter.
- Implemented different projects with the team. I worked in more than 20 website projects, involving coding(Joomla, HTML/CSS) and Visual Design for websites.

ECI.SOFT

Web Designer, Taiwan October 2011 - September 2013

- · Collected and organised the requirements from customers for supporting decision.
- · Built UI flow and wireframe and prototypes.

SKILLS

- Expert Adobe Creative Suite, Illustration, Sketch, Zeplin, HTML5, CSS/SASS and Visual Studio.
- Intermediate Pug/Jade, Jquery, Javascript, Boostrap, Npm, CSS animations, Git and Github
- · Learning Invision, Gulp, POSTCSS.

Achievements

- #Struggles Nominated for best cover design in Taiwan
 This book has sold more than 2,000 copies in Taiwan.

 https://www.books.com.tw/products/0010734823
- "The Life of Homeless Dog" Project published by a Wuo-Wuo Magazine.
 Wo Bao Bao is the only magazine in Taiwan that combines design to illustrate issues with animals and raise awareness about endangered species. I cooperated with Wuo-Wuo as a commissioned illustrator and created visuals for the magazine. The magazine is now popular and well-known in Taiwan.
- National College Student Research Scholarship from Ministry of Science and Technology in Taiwan.

I produced and designed an Augmented reality eco-education project. It was experimented at Yong Long Primary School and it received good feedback from the students. The project was later awarded the Scholarship from the Ministry of Education.

Education

Asia University Taiwan (2006 - 2011)

Bachelor of Arts degree in Department of Digital Media Design GPA 82.47 Subjects | Animate and Web design.

Languages

- · Mandarin (native)
- English (intermediate)